Next, we would like to welcome Mr. Ma from EA.
EA is used in various projects as a Marvellous Designer.
I believe Mr. Ma will teach you some very professional techniques.
Please give him a round of applause.
Hello, everyone.
It's a pleasure to be here at this conference.
Thank you for the invitation.
Thank you for giving us this opportunity.
Let me introduce myself briefly.
I am from EA Crete, Shanghai.
I am currently working as an FC,
which is an illegal football team.
I am the team leader of the Illegal World Cup.
I am mainly responsible for the World Cup.
I can show you some projects I have created.
I have put two projects here.
This is a landscape painting.
It is a project of the Illegal World Cup.
This is the Illegal World Cup.
This is also a project of the Illegal World Cup.
This is a project of the Illegal World Cup.
We are very pleased to have Mr. Ma here today.
We are high on the bucket list.
This project is a project of the Illegal World Cup.
We manage it with our studio.
This is a project of the Illegal World Cup.
This is an effort to hopefully make our 30-day project
as much as possible.
We get a lot of feedback.
This project is very, very impressive.
So, please take a look for yourself.
Now, we would like to introduce Mr. Ma.
Please raise your hand if you wouldn't mind.
He will start from his debut.
Okay.
We will introduce Mr. Ma.
Next, Mr. Ma will introduce the idea of an interface.
You are a designer and the director of the Illegal World Cup.
We are style-oriented, and don't need to show too much of the fabric and materials.
There is another student who said that when we reach the last 30% of the process,
we will have to go through a process of repeated adjustments.
This is actually a problem that we face in our company.
This process is quite low-level.
You will find that how you adjust it seems to be a bit poor.
Everyone will have to make their own choices.
I am here, wasting my time, going straight to ZBrush, and I have already lost my class, right?
This is because of our project.
Our project will allow us to reach a very high level of completion in the process.
So...
I am here,
and I would like to share some of my experiences with you all.
Basically, when we go from MD to ZBrush,
we will only adjust some of the poses that we need to make.
We won't adjust the composition too much in the high-level process.
We may only add a few.
Because MD is based on real-life physics.
It is very natural.
Because the game is based on real-life physics, it is very realistic.
So, I have summarized three points here.
This is my own way of making MD.
I will separate them and share them with you all.
Of course, there is no fixed standard for this.
This is just my personal experience.
Let's take a look at the comparison first.
Before we start, I would like to recommend you all to use the short circuit in the MD module library as a starting point.
Because it is very similar to our original version.
We can use it as a full-fledged prototype.
The prototype is actually a kind of foundation.
It can be used to make various kinds of clothes.
It is not only a starting point.
We can also clearly see that the short circuit part is actually our prototype.
The reason why we use it is because it is a prototype.
Because it is a prototype.
It is simple enough.
It is easy for us to modify.
We can directly run the program.
There are some positioning lines on it.
And some marking lines for the front and back panels.
These are all very easy tools to use.
Today, I have prepared a case.
This is also one of the clothes in our project.
Today, I will use this case as an example.
I will share some of my production techniques and ideas.
This prototype.
Because it is a prototype.
Maybe in reality, we can't find a copy of it.
When we observe this reference,
we need to consciously refer to it.
We need to consciously refer to it.
And then we can draw a simple scale.
And then we can ignore its material and structure.
We are adjusting the size,
and the size ratio.
And then we can adjust the size,
This step is very simple.
And of course, it is very important.
And then we can adjust the size,
and the size ratio.
This is our prototype.
For me, if you want to go further and have a higher degree of completeness, this step is a necessary step.
This is an example I recorded.
At the beginning, we can open the document in the library.
We can use the default version.
Its
We can delete it.
After that, we can do it directly.
It matches what we are using now.
Because now it is very simple and there is no problem.
It can be solved and there will be no problem.
Before we start recording, we need to optimize its file.
To optimize the file, we need to adjust the flexibility of the program.
Just like we did just now, we need to adjust the flexibility of the program.
Just like we did just now.
And now, we will start to reverse the curve.
We can adjust the volume.
The reverse curve is very important.
Don't make the curve too small.
We need to stop all the places with a curve.
We can use this...
Wait.
I want to pause the video.
Let me stop the video.
If there is no problem, then we can go back to normal.
When we are choosing the network line tool,
Sometimes, if there is a curve on the board, it will show up.
If you don't delete this curve,
we may have to adjust it to match the situation.
It's not very smooth.
So I used a benchmarking tool here.
This way, we can control it with a thin point tool.
If we drag it out, it's also a process of uniform change.
It won't have a strange curve.
It's very useful for us to adjust the smoothness of the curve.
This is the step we just started.
Let's clean up all these files first.
The purpose is to make it easier for us to edit the board.
We will edit and close all these.
According to...
the standard structure of the clothes.
When we connect the two boards,
we want it to be at 180 degrees on the board.
This way, from the side, it will be a very smooth curve.
Instead of some sharp corners.
These are the things we pay attention to at the beginning.
It's also a costume.
If you want to walk very far, you still have to pay attention to these things.
At the beginning, when we have done these things,
we will start...
to adjust it.
First, adjust the underarm.
It's because of the clothes.
And it's a coat.
We can't let it...
become very tight.
The underarm is not comfortable.
Then, we will directly go to the belt.
We will make a big nose.
Run around.
Okay.
No, no, no.
I will talk first.
After that, we will come back to you.
At the beginning, we will...
adjust it quickly.
We don't need to be very precise.
Because this process...
must be repeated.
Now, we have repeated adjustments.
Everything is very simple.
It's also very fast.
We don't need to change anything.
It's just that we have to...
often observe and refer to it.
And then,
look at our clothes now.
How is its speed?
So, in the second part, we will adjust...
the amount of the underarm first.
What is its amount?
To compare and refer.
We may feel that...
there is a little more at the back.
Right?
At the back, we will drag it a little.
So, from...
when we do it,
we still have to make sure that...
no matter from which angle,
our clothes will be smooth.
Right?
Our clothes in real life are also...
If you find that...
this clothes...
There may be a pointy corner here.
That only shows that...
their material is...
I think...
It's not good.
It's too detailed.
Then, we can put that here.
Show the length of the line.
Open the length of the line.
This will help us...
to observe very objectively...
whether there is...
a difference...
between the lines...
when we want to sew.
From the very beginning,
we don't need to...
make very precise adjustments.
Because...
it's possible that...
when we adjust it just now,
we find that...
the length of the line...
may be a little wider.
So,
we change the length of the line again.
This is actually...
a process...
that is...
invalid.
From the beginning,
we still need to...
make sure that...
the length of the line...
is...
from the most intuitive feeling...
we can see...
how the original pattern...
looks like.
It's the same as...
what we are adjusting now.
This is the same.
We will adjust...
the length of the line...
at the end.
This is very important.
This...
will save us...
a lot of time.
That is...
we don't do...
this...
before we are sure...
we may...
intentionally...
adjust...
the length of the line...
of the sleeve.
Like this.
But...
because...
we are...
working together...
and...
our...
original pattern...
is also...
very accurate.
So...
the length of the line...
of the sleeve...
may be...
inaccurate.
The rest of the...
length of the line...
is completely...
OK.
No problem.
This...
is what...
we need to worry about.
That is...
we need to...
adjust...
the length...
of the line...
so that...
the length...
of the line...
is wider...
so that...
it feels...
a bit...
loose.
But...
it is not loose.
It may be...
a bit...
loose.
So...
now...
it is...
more...
accurate.
That is...
now...
we still...
need to...
delete...
the line...
of the sleeve.
Because...
we think...
there is no problem...
with the length of the line.
Of course...
we need to...
adjust...
the length...
of the line...
first.
When...
we...
make...
the sleeve...
we must...
I don't recommend...
adding some points...
on the top.
This way...
you can...
adjust...
the length...
of the line...
in the end.
Maybe...
at the end...
when we say...
the material...
you can...
add some points.
Because...
we don't know...
how to do it.
Now...
we need to...
add some points...
on the top.
That is...
the length...
of the line...
is...
very...
important.
That is...
how can we adjust...
the length...
of the line?
First...
we need to...
look at...
the length...
of the line...
and...
if...
the length...
of the chest...
is...
appropriate.
Then...
the sleeve...
is...
we can...
use...
to...
let me...
look...
What...
It's to inspect...
the relationship...
between...
the clothes and...
the body.
Or we can...
школ我說...
or you can...
check if...
the shape is fine...
then...
we can...
use this...
point pressure to...
adjust theungen.
I think...
the event...
has been happened...
to these types of...
this type of things.
let me tell you more...
it's...
If...
this kind of clothes...
This is what we often check to see if your clothes fit or not.
It's also a very good tool.
There is one more thing.
If your sewing line is too big,
the fabric will turn red as soon as it is stretched.
If you have a lot of sewing lines in both sections,
the other section will definitely be red.
I will make a quick summary here.
At the beginning, the first step is to cut the fabric.
Cut the fabric as clean as possible.
Adjust it at any time.
And we don't have to worry about adjusting it.
We still need to correct it.
We try to remove this part of the sleeve.
The rest are all straight lines.
Don't let it go in the middle.
There are no lines.
Of course, the point of the waistline is a good support point.
And its positioning line can be retained.
The second step is very basic.
It's a joint version.
The one that was adjusted at the beginning must be a joint version.
This will make it difficult to match.
Let's adjust it.
Then, make good use of the anti-reverse sewing line
and the cover version.
When we adjust it,
we can better observe the relationship between our clothes and our body.
We can also observe our upper body.
Under the influence of the sleeve,
what kind of effect does it have?
Because there are a lot of classmates,
everyone is counting together.
In fact, your sleeve may not fit your upper body.
Right?
Because of the relationship between the sleeve and the anti-reverse sewing line,
you can't see it.
It may be that there are a lot of lines in some places.
This is very inconsequential.
So I suggest that you adjust the cover first.
Then, the pressure is just as I said.
This is a good way to see the sagging of our clothes.
And where the anti-reverse sewing line is.
You can see it at a glance.
The first step is basically the same.
Just sit down.
These four points are almost the same.
You can go down.
There is a second similarity.
The similarity is actually that
we need to observe our reference or original clothes more closely.
Some structures of clothes.
That is, we want to look at the position of its zipper,
the position of the sewing line,
and what details are on this clothes.
We want to play as much as possible with some of its styles and details.
That is, we can imagine in our mind
what we need to do with these sewing lines.
This is the effect of the anti-reverse sewing line.
So we can just press and hold the button,
and just click.
At the beginning,
I recommended that you use this
sewing line tool
directly to mark the line.
In fact, for me, this tool is very, very useful.
Because it's just like a brush.
It can
If we want to draw a line here, we can use it to mark it.
We don't need to make it very accurate.
In the beginning, we can make a rough one,
because it's easy to learn.
There are only two points.
If I can't observe it properly,
I need to draw this mark line.
Then we can observe it again.
Then it will be more convenient to sell it.
When making these lines,
no matter if it's right or wrong,
we put what we see in the eyes first.
This step is also very fast.
Because we may have ignored its texture and structure at the beginning.
This step may be more complicated.
We can push some small details back and forth.
For example, which lines should be marked first.
Like here, we can also use the internal line.
We can use the internal line to draw.
These points are deleted.
In fact, the more points, the better.
It's convenient for us to draw.
In this process, in fact,
if we find that this line is also a bit difficult,
we still need to adjust it.
But anyway,
I recommend you to draw these lines
after you have drawn the structure.
Then we can use it.
For example, we can use the horizontal line here.
For the horizontal line,
we can use a more accurate one.
Maybe you want to make it wider and wider.
Two eyes 1.5.
This is a way to adjust it.
Or you can add it first,
and then we can make it wider.
In the early stage,
you still have to try to
simplify it as much as possible.
Here I may feel that
my eyes are a little narrower.
Actually, you can select and adjust it together.
This way, you can adjust it more accurately.
We found that
after we finished all the asymmetrical things
in this line,
because there are two lines
in the same order,
there are two rhythm lines
that are asymmetrical.
So we have to finish this kind of thing here.
Before this step,
we will try our best
to do all the asymmetrical things well.
Otherwise,
we may have an external problem.
We also try our best
to be efficient and efficient.
Try to be as accurate as possible.
There is an answer to this question.
We can look at this reference.
It is
two pieces of the same picture.
We are just
I understand that
it may be cut like this.
But
you don't have to worry about it.
It's just like this.
So we
have to use these rhythm lines
to draw it out
and mark it out.
And then
we will look at it in general.
Is it okay?
But here we can also
do something else.
When doing the other side,
because it may be a cross,
a cross section,
I don't put it together first.
Because
I may have to adjust it later.
So I put it together first.
And then
the horizontal line can also be
This rhythm line can also be copied.
From this version
to the next version
It is also
more convenient.
After doing these,
we will observe more.
This clothes
These lines are what we want.
Where can it be changed?
It's easy to change at this stage.
We don't have to adjust the version.
We just take these lines out.
Just put them together.
I don't think there's a problem.
We can
of course cut it.
Because our
zipper is cut diagonally.
Diagonally.
Here I
We can use
Because I
I feel
There should be no problem.
So
Just,
We still
there's a custom version.
It's
a new one
A new version
We adjust it
more and more convenient.
That's a reason
I already approved it.
Now we need
Still using this
Six-line building
This
tool
We do
annya
Just
Can we
We can select the location we want to open.
We still need to observe the position of the chain.
Because we started from the middle,
the chain is also constructed like this.
There are two chains on both sides.
Now we mark these places of the chain.
This is a very detailed adjustment of the chain.
After our observation and consideration,
we need to analyze the structure of the chain based on reality.
We also need to consider the differences between the chain and the reference.
We also need to combine our own understanding to adjust it.
If you don't feel like adjusting it,
you can modify it immediately and then try again.
Because the cost of adjusting it at this stage is very low.
The process of connecting is very fast.
I don't need to solve anything.
Here I use the reference tool to open the title.
I can calculate it.
We can use the GPU first.
The GPU calculates it very quickly.
But I only recommend the previous one.
It builds up very quickly.
Look at our clothes.
It already has three layers of wearable pants.
Maybe the machine will calculate it faster.
Now we are all in the circle.
We want to make the chain different.
We need to cut the different materials first.
We need to pull these wires first.
We still need to adjust the reference line at all times.
At this stage,
we still need to be more precise when it comes to the middle.
Because if the reference line is not particularly good,
we may have some problems with the reference after we do it.
There may be some problems.
There may be some problems with the reference after we do it.
Because the reference line at this point is not completely straight.
We need to cut all these wires.
Then we can give it a new material.
Like this blue one,
we will give it a skin.
We can adjust its brightness.
You can see that right now the intelligence of your smartphone,
What you are using for the reference line now,
the lighting settings of the reference between the tape,
it is shown in the building.
But what happened is that the effect of it was birdie design of the Xlike world.
Now let's see if we have made the difference.
We can see that
the difference of the reference line difference between the YouTube video
is actually,
kind of different,
OK.
Is this right?
Okay, the GPU is still very fast.
This is also a simple summary.
The first point is to use a line to mark and adjust.
This process may involve the adjustment we made.
Although the first step is to adjust a large line,
it may not be suitable for some parts.
This part needs to be adjusted in time,
before there is a cut.
In our case, the cost is relatively low.
This is the second point.
The second point is to mark the cut of the board.
Because the board,
the straighter it is,
the easier it is for everyone to adjust.
So we don't need to cut where there is no need to cut.
Just replace it with this internal line.
So the question is,
how can we determine whether this thing is cut or not?
How to judge whether this board is cut or not?
Of course,
different people know that
we need to cut it.
Because the two pieces of fabric are the same.
And when they are put together,
the texture and the fold are different.
For these different textures,
we need to cut them.
But for the same texture,
do we need to cut it?
Why do we need to cut it?
Or why not cut it?
This needs to be observed
in some of the structures of our clothes.
For example,
there is a seam line.
And we need to check if there are two pieces of fabric
that need to be used.
For example,
the top part,
which is similar to a suit,
the shoulder part is cut.
Because this is a special structure,
a special shape.
So we need to cut it.
But the waist part is also cut.
Because it needs to have a waist.
The body and the waist
have a certain amount of difference.
So we still need to cut this part.
Basically,
we can't cut it.
We can cut it in this way.
The rest can be regulated
as we don't need to cut it.
The main point of this step is
in the structure.
We need to adjust it carefully.
Because this structure is a protection
for similarity and style.
Because,
in addition to the support of the inner line,
we can observe more clearly
the characteristics of the clothes.
This helps us to further adjust
the fabric and the inner line.
So this way,
the fabric and the inner line
are integrated.
Of course,
we don't need to adjust it too much.
Because in the first step,
we have already determined
its large proportion.
The last step is to
make some minor adjustments.
We still need to observe more.
Of course,
there is also a point
that you don't need to
make all the structures.
Which structures don't need to be made?
It depends on whether it affects
the shape of the clothes,
the style,
the width,
and the shape of the fabric.
However,
we can take a look at
the following.
For reference,
the two card holes at the bottom,
the bag,
and the bottom of the back,
there may be a small layer.
The seam line may not be
on the surface.
Because in our clothes,
we can see that
there are many layers.
For example,
the inner side of the zipper
is also a seam line.
It may be more than one seam line.
And the bag on the back,
the bag on the back,
for reference,
is more like a decoration.
It affects us.
The whole body shape
is not so much affected.
If you want to do it,
you also need to
make sure that
the seam line is well determined.
I still have to ignore
the parts that affect
my viewing.
I have to ignore
these small structures first.
But besides the seam line,
there is also a strong
elastic band
or rope.
It affects the shape of our clothes.
We still need to add it.
Because this is a step
of similarity.
So this is also very important.
The third point is the material.
The material is to adjust
the texture of the fabric.
There may be some small details
like what I just said.
The material,
the whole type of fabric,
the pattern of the fabric,
the details are all very important.
In fact,
MDU has provided a lot of
them.
Just some pre-made
pre-settings
are basically enough
unless you really have
some special requirements.
And this fabric is very special.
We can see that
there are always a lot of pre-settings.
The right table
is provided by the official
Because there is a list of what kind of cloth you are using.
You can probably use it on any clothes.
They have already made a summary.
If you need it, you can contact the official website and they will provide it to you.
There are some clothes that are not available in one layer of cloth.
At this time, we may need to use a custom layer.
Usually, when we use custom layers, we also use two layers.
In real life, it is a double layer of clothes.
We definitely need to use custom layers for this.
We can also look at our winter clothes.
It is definitely not just one layer.
It has a rich layer on the surface.
How is it?
What is the material of the inner layer and the outer layer?
Is it the same?
These are all things that we can see in real life.
Another thing is that you may really want your clothes to look thicker and heavier.
Now we can also make the clothes thicker.
This is the main thing.
This is mainly a...
This is a material adjustment.
A small sample.
Wait a second.
I can't play it.
I'll take a look.
I think it's fine.
It's fine.
No problem.
I'm not in a hurry.
I might need to put the file down.
Wait a moment.
Let me see.
I have this.
Wait a moment. Let me take it down.
Wait a moment.
Okay, let's try again and see if it works.
It suddenly broke.
It's like this again.
It seems to be a bit of a problem.
Okay, let's take a look at this first.
At the beginning, when we were doing the color, we definitely had to distinguish
which parts we had to do.
Which materials.
We still have to look at it in the reference.
It's not that we come up and choose all of them at once.
We still have to distinguish.
Now we choose the materials we want to do the color layer.
Go directly to it.
We use the color layer to the inside.
Okay.
Because in our project,
we want it to have a very correct seal relationship.
Because when you color the layer,
its seal line relationship will change.
The layer you color, it will only seal with itself.
I'm going to color the other layer with the same seal line.
Let me drag it a little bit.
I'm sure everyone will have this problem, right?
It's not stable.
When the clothes have more layers,
when the clothes are made with more layers,
there will definitely be this problem.
Sometimes the clothes in a single piece will also have this problem.
Like this one, it's plain wear problem.
We have to use layers to quickly adjust it.
Use our curtain layer,
this coat,
and give it a layer.
And then widely sort it out.
But once you make it stable,
we must make this layer 0.
Because this layer will have a very clear separation of 1-layer and 2-layer materials.
So we still want our materials to have the same capacity.
So we just use it to solve some of the problems.
To see the texture of the fabric, we need to reduce the particle diameter.
After reducing the particle diameter, we can see the texture of the fabric.
Because if the particle diameter is too high, it may have some gaps.
It's not clear enough.
Then we select the fabric of the clothes.
Here we use nylon.
We use this material.
We also use a single-layer material for the inner side.
The inner side will be more flexible.
There are actually two inner layers in MDG.
It is specially provided for us.
Then we can use...
We can use a softer material for the inner side.
We can also give a color to slightly distinguish.
Here it may be...
I don't want to pull it in there.
After cutting, we need to check it carefully.
Then we can solve the problem.
At this point, we may start to waste time.
This is the end of the video.
It is related to the machine.
Actually, we can see that there are already some defects in it.
At this point, we may need to observe for reference.
In this video, there is no reference picture.
The reference picture is broken.
Let's think about it based on the previous impression.
Maybe the amount of the fabric.
The shape of the fold is not enough to support it.
It may be different from the texture we want in terms of shape.
Because its amount is not enough.
So we may need to make it a little bit more.
Here, because we are still in the process of adjustment.
We are pursuing the similarity of its texture.
So it takes a lot of time every time.
We can reverse the fire.
Reverse the fire to the rest of the surface.
Let's take a piece of fabric separately to test.
Is it the effect we want?
All of them.
If the effect is correct.
We can apply it to all of the clothes.
All of them.
Just go to the factory.
The reverse fire used here.
After the reverse fire.
Its sewing line will still be there.
It is equivalent to your edges are curved.
Your clothes will not fall down.
So this is a very good method.
I can analyze it.
We want to make its surface a little bit more.
That is, we can adjust its fine-tuning rate and fine-tuning rate.
Of course, this amount.
In fact, because our version is actually more accurate.
We don't need to open it too much in this process.
Let it have a little.
In fact, the effect will be very obvious.
That's the inner layer.
That's here.
We can see.
Its clothes.
Although it has this shape.
But it seems to be like our ideal life.
It's the ideal.
This kind of cloth.
The shape of the fold is not the same.
It seems to be.
In the sky.
On the other side of the cloth.
Some.
After it shrinks.
It's just on its original fold.
It's getting deeper.
It's not evenly scattered all over the body.
Here.
We can use this pressure layer.
We can move the inner layer.
It's like a dragon's head.
That's how it works.
Let's make it this cloth.
The inner and outer layers are separated.
Let it have a free movement.
Don't lift it in the middle.
Don't let it stick to the cloth first.
Let it really be two layers of cloth.
Then we can.
Put his pressure out.
You can use a 0.1 first.
It's the process of accelerating it.
It's quite far.
In fact, you can use 0.1.
It's also possible.
Just slowly.
It's more natural.
Calculate it again.
In this process.
It must be.
Need to.
Confirm repeatedly.
We want to do.
What kind of material is this cloth?
You may spend more material.
And then.
Adjust more.
So.
We want.
His.
This.
How much is the amount of material?
When all of us.
When you adjust.
Adjust well.
That's what we want.
These amounts.
That's what we're giving him.
Apply to other materials.
Because.
That's definitely a must.
We.
Half a piece.
No problem.
This.
This step.
In fact, there is no problem.
We can also put these small bags.
All of these.
Add up.
These are actually.
Similar to the style.
Things.
It won't.
Too much.
Affect your version.
And.
Just.
Behind.
This.
Loosen.
The.
It's.
When you do this.
Definitely.
You need to put your sewing line.
Connect yourself.
To make it clear.
Because you need it.
Stable.
It's.
Three layers.
Together.
It's.
That's all.
OK.
It's a few.
Yeah.
So.
In this.
Public.
Good.
I think.
Continue.
Just a simple summary.
In fact.
There is not much.
For summary.
This step.
In fact.
Mainly.
Adjusting.
Our.
The fabric.
Performance.
And.
Some.
Details.
Of.
How to.
Cut.
Our.
Take.
Matters.
We definitely won't make major changes to this part.
If we need to change our version,
that means we didn't do a good job on the front.
A proper design plus a proper fabric
will allow our clothes to have a higher level of flexibility.
There is one more thing I would like to say.
The first two steps must be done well.
The first two steps are not time-consuming.
You can make quick adjustments.
You can adjust it as you like.
There is no need to worry about the performance of the machine.
If you didn't do a good job on the first two steps,
you can start with some decoration and structure,
or double layers.
Later on, if you find that the structure of your clothes is not good enough,
or there are too many layers,
then you can adjust the version again.
It will be very troublesome.
Especially since my clothes are quite complete.
For example,
the clothes on the top,
there are a lot of pieces.
Some clothes have a lot of layers.
If you adjust it again,
you will definitely
need to look at all the layers.
It is very difficult to adjust it now.
So when we are working on it,
Hello?
This is a good question.
When we are working on it,
we need to think about
how to make it look like
the same as art.
First,
we need to make it look bigger.
How to make it look bigger?
No matter what kind of clothes you are making,
whether it is a complicated or simple one,
we can all use this kind of thinking
to make it look bigger.
Then,
the sharing of cases
is basically
gone.
Then,
I will have some
small suggestions.
Maybe some small techniques.
Like
many layers of clothing.
For example,
the clothes below.
It has four layers on the body.
There is a bag on the outside.
How can we make our clothes stable?
What we are doing
is definitely
a solution.
It won't fly.
It is a very stable bag.
For this step,
we need to manage our layers well.
We must not
have excess layers.
When we
make sure our clothes are stable,
when we make sure our clothes are stable,
we need to regulate all layers.
We need to make sure
that there are no excess layers
on all layers.
This way,
the balance between your clothes
is correct.
It will be more stable.
The other thing is
your machine's performance.
There is no other way.
If you want,
you can add more layers.
The more layers you have,
the better your machine will be.
These are some small techniques.
This is what we have in the video.
How to do with the layers?
We can add a layer
and adjust it quickly.
After adjusting it,
we must go back.
We can adjust it quickly.
Sometimes your clothes are torn.
It's hard to take off.
We can use this grid.
This is the simplest way.
We can adjust it first
and then we can add more layers.
There are some
fixed tools.
There are some fixed tools.
Many students
may have some difficulties
when using the grid.
New students
may have some difficulties.
They want this kind of curve.
They don't use our model.
They use the grid to adjust the shape.
This is the original model.
You don't have to go to Zbrush
and make it.
When we use the grid,
Then I feel that
people want a solid profile.
People who use this model
At first it can help them
to have full of 3D.
We choose a useful tool and
press it down.
The från is fused to the 3D.
The from is fused to the 3D.
It is measured and calculated.
And then the third one,
I fixed it on a transparent board.
I wanted it to be vertical, so I made it vertical first.
The transparent board we just talked about,
there are many different ways to do it.
We can all use transparent boards.
We can use transparent boards to fix the opening and the distance.
Of course we can also use a fixed pin.
The reason we use fixed pins is that
we have a longer opening,
and if we use a fixed pin,
it will have a little bit of a gap.
There seems to be a drawback here.
If you use a fixed pin, you don't want it to be torn down.
So it definitely has a drawback.
But we don't want to have a problem with that.
So we don't want to have a problem with that.
But the transparent board,
if you look at it from the side,
it's actually the same as the one piece of this cloth.
It's part of this board.
They are solved together.
They also go down with nature.
So this is a very good method.
I hope it can help you a little bit.
When you're solving some problems.
This is a process of making a transparent board quickly.
I'm not going to spoil all the time.
Let's start.
We can see there's an opening here.
If we don't interfere with it,
this opening will definitely fail.
Because it's based on a plain picture.
And our modeling posture is just a T pose.
If we have some poses in our body,
it may be able to do a flip.
But we're not doing it with a transparent board.
We're not doing it with a transparent board.
And we're not doing it with a transparent board.
If you are in a default situation, it will definitely not come back.
When we are doing this version,
we can actually directly
use the tool to create the version.
Just create it directly.
There is a creative version here.
The point is that we just need to make our opening correct.
We don't need to think about how long or how accurate it is.
We just need to get the angle right.
That's the most important thing.
I put it on the board here
because I want to make the opening correct as much as possible.
And the opening I want to make
I want it to open here.
So I pull it to the back here to make the opening correct.
But whether it's long or short,
you don't need to think about these things.
We can just do it with the free-for-all tool.
As long as you can confirm that the probability of your for-all is 1,
you don't need to worry about the extra material.
Then we
add this material to the side of the front.
It will automatically move to the side of the other piece of material.
Then we can give it a single material.
And then reduce the transparency to 0.
And then like this.
If you want to make it a little harder,
you can do it like I did.
You can also freeze it.
But if you freeze it,
it may not be very smooth.
You can freeze it and let it count.
After we reduce the frequency to 1,
it will not be selected in the 3D system.
It won't affect our fire operation.
We can directly use it to select the next material.
OK.
That's all I want to share with you today.
Thank you very much for your wonderful sharing, Mr. Ma.
Thank you, Mr. Ma.
Let's see if there are any questions from the audience.
Let's continue the conversation.
OK.
Thank you, Mr. Ma.
Thank you.
Now, it's the time for the Profile Mitglate ENT,
to comment on a lot of requests for us today.
First,
is there any process
you are searching for us to analyse,
via주세요?
When you don't have a cologne layer,
the connection between the cologne layers is correct.
But when we make the cologne layer,
the relationship between the cologne layer and the cologne layer
will only be the same as the cologne layer.
So when we make the cologne layer,
we only want the surface to be the same as the cologne layer.
Think about it.
In fact, we don't want the fabric of the cologne layer to be the same as the cologne layer.
Just like when you wear clothes,
you don't care what the fabric of your clothes looks like.
We just want the surface to be the same as the cologne layer.
Is it the same if the cologne layer only holds up the outer clothes?
It does have this function,
but the more important function is the way the fabric is folded.
That's what we want.
We want to experience the texture of the fabric.
You mean to say that if you wear the same clothes as the cologne layer,
but you want the fabric to be more natural,
and you don't want the fabric to be the same as the cologne layer?
Yes.
It's not that we want the fabric to be more natural.
We just want the texture to be the same as the cologne layer.
The quality of the fabric you have
is different from the fabric of the clothes you wear.
The effect is different, right?
The shape of the fold is different.
The reason we make the cologne is to see if it has a good display effect on the outer surface.
Now I can explain it to you clearly.
Thank you.
First of all, thank you, Mr. Ma, for your sharing.
It's very detailed and very useful.
Thank you.
And then my question is, when you introduced yourself,
I know you are the leader of the illegal clothing group.
Yes.
I would like to ask, in our game company,
what are the requirements for the position of the clothing department?
Because I myself am in the clothing industry,
and I also have our sister software club.
In fact, the two softwares are very similar in many ways.
Personally, I am very interested in the game industry,
so I want to know if there will be a big opportunity.
Of course, if you have the experience of the clothing industry,
that's great.
We are the leader of the illegal clothing group, right?
I think you are very professional.
Because we study ourselves through observation.
Unlike you, who has a professional knowledge reserve,
we know what is reasonable and what is not reasonable in this clothing.
Right?
Of course, you have such experience,
it is very valuable and very good.
That is, you just need to pull it out, and you will be able to wear it.
If you apply your professional knowledge to our software,
that's no problem.
That's OK.
What I'm afraid of is that you will be the first to guess, right?
But when we used AMD, you couldn't use it at all.
This is what we don't want to see.
So if you get to the game industry, there will still be a chance?
Of course.
In the future, we will invite our colleague, Zhu Minghua,
to share some of the content about our company's recruitment.
OK, thank you.
My question is more related to the question he asked earlier.
If we are doing a broken-down layer,
is it more of a layer of material calculation?
And then the inner layer and the outer layer,
they all have friction.
So this is an additional layer of material,
which makes it more realistic.
Yes, yes.
Right?
Yes, yes, yes.
There is no problem with this understanding.
OK.
Hello, I have a question.
In the case of the design of the clothing,
what kind of form of the model do you use?
What are your experiences?
Can you share with us?
OK.
In fact, we are using a lot of different models.
We are using the same model,
and we are also using the same design as the model.
But the way we use it is different.
We are using the same model,
but we are using the same design as the model.
So what's the difference?
We are using the same design,
and we are also using the same model.
So what's the difference?
Can you share with us?
OK.
In fact, we want to make a beautiful clothing.
The more exaggerated your movements are,
the better the results you may display.
We have to use T-pose in the project,
because we need to tie up
a lot of processes in the later process.
We have to use T-pose
to make it as good as possible
The model looks rich, and the texture is correct.
This is a difficult point.
If you just want to have a beautiful foldable model,
then of course your actions will determine what your foldable model looks like.
If you think about it, in the case of a T-Force,
you can calculate such a beautiful foldable model, right?
I can, I can express myself in a very important way.
If you look at the T-Force in more detail,
you can see the angle of the drop of the arm and the curve of the wrist.
Yes, why do we need to use the angle of the drop of the arm and the curve of the wrist?
Can I move it up a little bit?
For example,
because in the game,
most of the pose is still the arm down.
Just as we usually stand here,
our hand is still down.
We use this pose to make the weight of the foldable part of our sleeves look down.
If we lift our hands,
its weight will definitely be biased,
and if we put the shape of the foldable down,
it may be unnatural.
Yes.
This is also something we will have to do in the future.
We may need to
put our arms together and match it to our
standard, horizontal posture.
Yes.
Okay, thank you.
Hello, I want to ask if AI can help us
in the blockchain industry.
Good question.
What impact does it have?
This is definitely an inevitable trend, isn't it?
Our company is already training AI internally.
Of course, we are still in the early stages of it.
We are also working with the famous Ma Tianzhi
to provide some resources.
We are also exploring this area.
It may have an impact in the future,
but
we still have a lot of work experience,
art aesthetics,
and, how should I put it,
some experience in the project.
There may be a lot of limitations to your project.
It's not that
we don't know what kind of beautiful clothes we want to use.
You may have to think about what kind of
team you want to work with in the future.
You need to think about all of these.
For AI,
I think,
because it's developing so fast now,
one day in the future,
it will definitely be able to do very well.
But actually,
we don't need to think about it now.
I'm worried about that.
Because AI may have an impact on the entire industry.
Right?
Yes.
Hello, teacher.
I want to ask you about the
transparency aspect.
The most important thing is
whether there are constraints in the first place.
And then,
is it possible that
a certain character
can be explained
in real time?
Yes.
Do you think there are constraints
in the first place?
In the first place,
the constraints between the main character
and the main character
are very different.
Do you mean
I don't want to have constraints
or what?
It depends on the time.
In the past,
I don't want to have any
constraints.
We can,
if this is the opening effect
that you want in the end,
you can
Hello?
You can also
in the previous production
No, no, no.
We can use
the anti-activation sewing line.
We can have the board here,
right?
After the anti-activation,
the sewing line will not participate in the production.
The sewing line of the anti-activation board
is fixed.
will also be separated.
It won't affect you.
It won't restrict you.
You can put it here first.
It won't say that it may not be used later.
If you want to use it,
you can activate the board.
It has such an effect.
This can make it easy for you to adjust it flexibly.
Can you understand?
Yes, yes.
You can use the anti-activation board.
If you are in the middle...
If you are in the middle,
you can put it on the board.
Yes, yes.
If you are in the middle,
you can put it on the board.
Yes.
I don't know what kind of question
you want to express.
I don't understand
what kind of question
you want to express.
Yes.
I don't understand what kind of question
you want to express.
OK.
I just want to know
what kind of question
you want to express.
OK.
What I think is
the shape of the board
and its physical properties
are related.
You can set it up
It's not easy to stretch and it's harder.
For example, this section is also a triangular section.
When you give it a harder material,
it may be limited to, for example, 5 cm.
And then if you set it to a fabric that is easy to stretch,
then it may open this opening and slowly turn into,
for example, 7 cm or 10 cm,
because its stretching performance has changed.
Then your transition will be more natural.
For this transparent version,
one is actually your shape,
and it also includes purpose properties.
These are all properties that you can change at any time in the transparent version.
And the transparent version,
it is actually a larger fraction of the transformation,
rather than the fraction of point-to-point with a fixed needle.
Because the fraction of point-to-point with a fixed needle like this,
it is easy to have a problem where a certain point is stretched particularly seriously.
With the transparent version,
it is to directly distribute the force of one point on two sewing lines.
Thank you.
Are there any other questions?
Actually, I think the last question is about the interaction of multiple characters.
When you want to interact with multiple costumes and multiple roles,
do you need to pay attention to the fact that these characters will intermingle?
When you want to interact with multiple characters,
that is, you want it to have a kind of movement, right?
Yes.
For example, when we make a sword or make a knife,
this process is very important.
First of all, you have to ensure that it is in a stable state, right?
This is a very important point.
Next, we want it to be stable when it is moving.
This is also required for your animation.
Because you want it to make an animation,
and you want it to...
You have to do it with a lot of details.
Of course, our example is very low, right?
If we move too much when we are moving,
it will definitely intermingle.
So when you want to do this kind of animation calculation for sports,
your animation model settings must have a few points to pay attention to.
The first point is that your movement speed cannot be too large.
You can make your animation longer with each point,
so that the speed of each point will be very small.
Then the other point is that you have to calculate for a long time.
So maybe you have to calculate for a long time for each point,
so that you can maintain a state where your material is stable at any time.
It's not like we're doing it on a single layer.
If you drag it blindly, it will definitely be unstable, right?
Do you have any other questions?
Is it the answer you want?
Or do you want to ask the question again?
Thank you.
Do you have any other questions?
Yes.
I have a small request.
We have a day off.
Maybe we need a Chinese student to help us.
Say something.
I'm going to take a deep breath.
There's no electricity.
There is no power.
No electricity.
Thank you for your attention and time today.
Thank you for the official invitation.
Thank you for the teachers' sharing.
Now it's time to eat.
Give you 5 minutes to make a little advertisement.
Okay.
Thank you.
I am the head of the character department of EAQ Shanghai, my name is Zhu Minghua.
I am very happy to be here with you today.
Let me tell you a little bit about our studio.
Our studio is a studio that focuses on the solution of the supply of art assets.
Our company is located in Nanjing Xilu, the center of the city.
We were established in 2006, a few years ago.
Now we have more than 100 talented artists.
Our main job is to collaborate with the world's largest EA game studios,
and help them provide solutions for art.
In 2019, we rescheduled and became EA Crate.
That's why our name is EA Crate Shanghai.
Let's take a look at our current partners.
Liu Sports and Respawn.
I'm sure many of you are familiar with them.
They are partners of many companies, including their works,
Triple Effect, Maxis, Dice, Motif.
These are some of the projects we have been working on in the past two years.
They mainly focus on car racing.
Our biggest partner is Veefa.
Ma Chao, who just joined the Veefa team,
and Zhan Di, and Atex.
They are all our main partners,
including some of our long-term partners.
Now let's take a look at some of our favorite works.
These are some of our daily work.
These are basically all our main products.
These are our hair,
and our beard.
We have used the latest Scenic Hair technology.
This is a high-quality, high-performance hair and hair expression in the game.
This is a dynamic resolution effect.
In terms of design,
EA is still at an early stage in the hair design industry.
Basically, these are the games that are currently being implemented in the main game.
This is the actual product of the project that you just saw.
These are the backpacks.
Ma Chao personally built these in AMD.
Zhan Di.
There are also quite a lot of AMD products.
This is a combination of AMD and Scenic Hair.
We have a very high value for our assets,
because we want to ensure that our AMD will be able to reach the same standard
for both Scenic Hair and Scenic Hair assets.
This is our latest,
our fourth main product in China.
This is also our current production.
This is it.
Of course, there are also some stylized projects.
For example, this was launched in December last year.
We have provided a large number of art products.
There is also a heat-resistant Apex,
which has been operating for four years.
Is it broken?
Yes, it's broken.
Okay.
There's only one left.
Let's take a look at the picture.
Okay.
Yes, it's broken.
Of course, there is the plant and
plastic modeler series that we used to do.
And then we have our cute Syms,
the better body extension.
Right, other than the project,
we also have a lot of internal training,
You can see a lot of our works on the top of the page.
Okay, thank you everyone.
This is just a small advertisement.
We have a first-class team here,
first-class technology,
first-class cooperation partners,
and first-class project requirements.
So those who need it online or offline
can use this LV code.
The following links can also be linked to our product page.
And the email can also be linked to us.
Thank you everyone.
If you have any more information,
please feel free to contact us.
Sherry is in the public number.
If you have any questions, please feel free to ask.
Thank you everyone for your time.
Thank you.
Thank you for the wonderful sharing from the EA team.
If you want to join EA,
please don't miss this opportunity.
Time flies.
Our event is almost over.
Finally, we have entered
the most exciting part of the show.
We are now going to select
two second-place winners and one first-place winner.
First, let's have the two teachers from Guangxi
to help us select the two second-place winners.
I want to pick one.
Pick one.
I want to pick myself.
I'm very sure.
No. 26 and No. 54.
Which one is which?
Are they all here?
Are they?
I don't know.
Okay, thank you.
We will do a registration here later.
In addition, please come up
and help us select the first-place winners.
The first-place winners.
Yes, yes, yes.
Thank you.
The second-place winners
have the right to use the marketing list.
In addition to the right to use the software,
the first-place winners also have the right to use the software.
They can also get a dedicated display
sponsored by Mingji.
So, the first-place winners.
Please come up.
No. 51.
Which one is it?
Congratulations to the winner.
Congratulations.
Okay, thank you very much.
The winners can add more information here later.
Then we can take a photo and leave a message
with our teacher today.
Thank you very much for participating in our event today.
We hope that if we can do more
in the future,
we will be able to participate more actively.
Thank you.